{"qid": "hard-yelp-0000", "question": "How many Home Organization businesses are there in Franklin, TN?", "answer": 4, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0001", "question": "How many Hair Salons businesses are there in Trooper, PA?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0002", "question": "How many Tours businesses are there in Wayne, PA?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0003", "question": "How many Southern businesses are there in Glenolden, PA?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0004", "question": "How many Brewpubs businesses are there in Lumberton, NJ?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0005", "question": "How many Wedding Planning businesses are there in Cinnaminson, NJ?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0006", "question": "How many Florists businesses are there in Lansdale, PA?", "answer": 5, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0007", "question": "How many Wholesale Stores businesses are there in Boise, ID?", "answer": 7, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0008", "question": "How many Discount Store businesses are there in Speedway, IN?", "answer": 1, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0009", "question": "How many Auto Glass Services businesses are there in Saint Petersburg, FL?", "answer": 5, "type": "how many business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0010", "question": "How many businesses are there in 18917 area of Dublin, PA?", "answer": 25, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0011", "question": "How many businesses are there in T5L 2L4 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 1, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0012", "question": "How many businesses are there in 19120 area of Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": 161, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0013", "question": "How many businesses are there in T6H 1M2 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 1, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0014", "question": "How many businesses are there in T6V 1B1 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 5, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0015", "question": "How many businesses are there in T5N 1R1 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 3, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0016", "question": "How many businesses are there in T5Y 2W7 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 5, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0017", "question": "How many businesses are there in T8H 2A2 area of Sherwood Park, AB?", "answer": 3, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0018", "question": "How many businesses are there in 08026 area of Gibbsboro, NJ?", "answer": 18, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0019", "question": "How many businesses are there in T5P 2S1 area of Edmonton, AB?", "answer": 1, "type": "business in total"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0020", "question": "Which Dentists business has the highest star rating in Wenonah, NJ?", "answer": "Nester & Wyckoff General Dentistry", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0021", "question": "Which Sandwiches business has the highest star rating in Garnet Valley, PA?", "answer": "Lancaster County Sausage", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0022", "question": "Which Restaurants business has the highest star rating in Affton, MO?", "answer": "Sushi Hana", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0023", "question": "Which Dry Cleaning business has the highest star rating in Sun City Center, FL?", "answer": "Amazing Cleaners", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0024", "question": "Which French business has the highest star rating in Indian Rocks Beach, FL?", "answer": "Cafe de Paris Bakery", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0025", "question": "Which ATV Rentals/Tours business has the highest star rating in Sparks, NV?", "answer": "SWARMFIRE", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0026", "question": "Which Videos & Video Game Rental business has the highest star rating in Nashville, TN?", "answer": "Gamestop", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0027", "question": "Which Periodontists business has the highest star rating in St Louis, MO?", "answer": "Nikodem Dental", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0028", "question": "Which Formal Wear business has the highest star rating in Deptford, NJ?", "answer": "Men's Wearhouse", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0029", "question": "Which Bars business has the highest star rating in Magnolia, NJ?", "answer": "The Laughing Fox Tavern", "type": "highest star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0030", "question": "Which Condominiums business has the highest review count in Tampa, FL?", "answer": "The Place At Channelside", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0031", "question": "Which Imported Food business has the highest review count in Santa Barbara, CA?", "answer": "El Sitio", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0032", "question": "Which Windshield Installation & Repair business has the highest review count in Lutz, FL?", "answer": "Gerber Collision & Glass", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0033", "question": "Which Diagnostic Imaging business has the highest review count in New Orleans, LA?", "answer": "All American Healthcare New Orleans", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0034", "question": "Which Restaurants business has the highest review count in Fortville, IN?", "answer": "Simeri's Italian", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0035", "question": "Which Bridal business has the highest review count in Ardmore, PA?", "answer": "Bijou Bridal & Special Occasion Ardmore", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0036", "question": "Which Pet Stores business has the highest review count in Oakville, MO?", "answer": "Treats Unleashed", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0037", "question": "Which Movers business has the highest review count in Cherry Hill, NJ?", "answer": "All My Sons Moving & Storage", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0038", "question": "Which Sushi Bars business has the highest review count in Carpinteria, CA?", "answer": "Sushi Teri", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0039", "question": "Which Periodontists business has the highest review count in Fairless Hills, PA?", "answer": "USA Dental Care", "type": "highest review count"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0040", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Uptown Delivery Pharmacy?", "answer": "94.10", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0041", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Residence Inn Tampa Suncoast Parkway at NorthPointe Village?", "answer": 28.08, "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0044", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Sublime Yoga and Wellness?", "answer": "45.92", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0045", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Duvall Flooring?", "answer": "48.89", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0046", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Bala Institute of Oral Surgery?", "answer": "68.82", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0048", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Maro Brothers' Discount Liquor Mart?", "answer": "23.50", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0049", "question": "What is the average review counts of businesses within a 5-mile radius from Studio 210 Salon?", "answer": "37.40", "type": "average review counts"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0050", "question": "Which is the nearest Chinese business to Sugar Mamas Custom Cakes?", "answer": "Hong Kong Restaurant", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0051", "question": "Which is the nearest Cooking Classes business to 5-Star Staffing Solutions?", "answer": "Sur La Table", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0052", "question": "Which is the nearest Orthopedists business to TNS Diamonds?", "answer": "Benjamin's On the Row", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0053", "question": "Which is the nearest Immigration Law business to MYNT Cannabis Dispensary Downtown Reno?", "answer": "Law Office Of Mark Mausert", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0054", "question": "Which is the nearest Himalayan/Nepalese business to Roller City?", "answer": "Himalaya Kabob Korner", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0055", "question": "Which is the nearest Divorce & Family Law business to Clearwater Dental Associates?", "answer": "Carey Leisure & Neal", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0056", "question": "Which is the nearest Bangladeshi business to Harcourts NV1?", "answer": "Dawat Fast Food & Restaurant", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0058", "question": "Which is the nearest Preschools business to Cumberland Transit?", "answer": "Primrose School of Nashville Midtown", "type": "nearest business"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0061", "question": "Can you recommend a Bars business with the highest star rating within a 5-mile radius of 2428 Nolensville Rd?", "answer": "H≈çru Sushi Kitchen", "type": "business recommendation"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0062", "question": "Can you recommend a Restaurants business with the highest star rating within a 5-mile radius of 540 Simpson Dr?", "answer": "San Marco Pasta", "type": "business recommendation"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0065", "question": "Can you recommend a Automotive business with the highest star rating within a 5-mile radius of 75 Queensway Dr?", "answer": "Take 5 Oil Change", "type": "business recommendation"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0066", "question": "Can you recommend a Shipping Centers business with the highest star rating within a 5-mile radius of 5930 Daley St?", "answer": "One Stop Hauling & Courier Services", "type": "business recommendation"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0069", "question": "Can you recommend a Restaurants business with the highest star rating within a 5-mile radius of 2 Engineer Rd?", "answer": "Petri Cafe", "type": "business recommendation"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0070", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Lawnside?", "answer": 2, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0071", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Terra Ceia?", "answer": 0, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0072", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Pipersville?", "answer": 3, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0073", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Tarpon springs?", "answer": 0, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0074", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Mt Laurel Township?", "answer": 0, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0075", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Glen Carbon?", "answer": 3, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0076", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Washington Township?", "answer": 2, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0077", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in McCordsville?", "answer": 0, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0078", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Franconia?", "answer": 0, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0079", "question": "How many businesses are not open currently in Maryland Heights?", "answer": 37, "type": "business not open"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0080", "question": "What is the average star rating of Limos businesses in St. Ann?", "answer": 5.0, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0081", "question": "What is the average star rating of Television Service Providers businesses in Saint Petersburg?", "answer": 1.5, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0082", "question": "What is the average star rating of Body Shops businesses in Brentwood?", "answer": 3.1, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0083", "question": "What is the average star rating of Asian Fusion businesses in Ladue?", "answer": 3.0, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0084", "question": "What is the average star rating of Pet Groomers businesses in Hermitage?", "answer": 2.8, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0085", "question": "What is the average star rating of Car Buyers businesses in Woodbury?", "answer": 2.0, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0086", "question": "What is the average star rating of Local Services businesses in Mount Holly?", "answer": 3.4, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0087", "question": "What is the average star rating of Arts & Entertainment businesses in Florissant?", "answer": 2.5, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0088", "question": "What is the average star rating of Structural Engineers businesses in Philadelphia?", "answer": 1.0, "type": "average star rating"}
{"qid": "hard-yelp-0089", "question": "What is the average star rating of Fitness & Instruction businesses in Ladue?", "answer": 4.5, "type": "average star rating"}
